brostrick.com 2015-06-10

# Brostrick Privacy Statement

**Brostrick Privacy Statement**

**Effective Date: 11/13/14**

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Statement describes the types of information Brostrick collects from and about you when you visit our website [www.brostrick.com](http://www.brostrick.com/) (“Site”) or use our mobile applications (each an “App”).  The Site and Apps are collectively the “Services.”  This Privacy Statement also explains how Brostrick may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

  * **Information You Provide**

Brostrick collects information from you when you choose to provide it to us.  This may include when you request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email list, use our Services, participate in a survey or promotion, or otherwise contact us.

The information we collect may include your name, address, email address, and telephone number.  If you use a third party service to link to or to communicate with us (such as a social network), we may receive certain information about you from the third party based on your registration and privacy settings on those third party services.

  * **Information Automatically Collected**

We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to collect certain information when you use our Services or interact with our emails and online or mobile advertisements.  For example, we may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you such as a device identifier or other information transmitted from your device, browser type, operating system, device model, software version, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, mobile or ISP carrier information, and the domain name from which you accessed the Services.

We also may collect information about your use of the Services, including the date and time you access the Services; the areas or pages of the Services that you visit; the amount of time you spend using the Services; the number of times you return; whether you open, forward, or click-through emails and ads; and other usage data.  We may also use third party advertisements to support our Services.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, or log files when they advertise on our Services, which may send these advertisers information, including your non-personal information.

_Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures._   You may adjust your browser or operating system settings to limit this tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Services or take full advantage of all of our offerings.  Check the “Help” menu of your browser or operating system to learn how to change your tracking settings or cookie preferences.  To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and your choices about not having this information used by certain Service Providers (defined below), please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).  On your mobile device, you can adjust your privacy and advertising settings to limit your tracking for advertising or control whether you receive more relevant advertising.  Note that our systems may not recognize Do Not Track headers or requests from some or all browsers.

  * **Information Collected From Other Sources**

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including social networks that you use to connect with Brostrick.  This information may include your name, user name, demographic information, updated address or contact information, interests, preferred language, activity and contacts on the social network, and publicly-observed data.  The information we may collect will depend on your registration and privacy settings on the applicable third-party service.

  * **Combination of Information**

We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including information you provide to us and information we automatically collect through our Sites and Apps, as well as information collected offline or from third party sources, to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our Services.

**INFORMATION USE**

Brostrick may use the information we collect from and about you to:

  * Provide services and communicate with visitors;
  * Develop new products or services;
  * Respond to your inquiries;
  * Provide you with customized Services content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Services or on other sites and apps;
  * Contact you with information, newsletters, and promotional materials from Brostrick or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
  * Contact you when necessary;
  * Review the usage and operations of our Services and improve our content, products, and services;
  * Address problems with the Services or our business;
  * Manage our telecommunications networks;
  * Protect the security or integrity of the Services and our business; and
  * As described to you at the point of data collection.

**INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**

Brostrick may disclose the information we collect from and about you (1) to our Service Providers, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Brostrick Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (3) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement or regulatory agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (4) to our select partners and affiliates that we believe may have offers of interest to you; and (5) as described to you at the point of collection.

Brostrick may also share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties for their marketing or analytics uses.

Brostrick may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business.  If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity.  In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties.  Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through this Services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

**SERVICE PROVIDERS**

Brostrick may contract with third parties to perform functions related to the Services (“Service Providers”).  Service Providers will have access to your personal information needed to perform their business functions, but may not use or share that personal information for purposes outside the scope of their functions related to the Services.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

For California residents:  Brostrick may share your personal information with third parties (including affiliated third parties which may not share the Brostrick name) for their direct marketing purposes.  Under California law, you may request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please contact us at contact@brostrick.com.

**PUBLIC FORUMS**

Any information you may disclose on our Services, such as in blogs, on message boards, or on other public areas on the Services, becomes public information.  Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

The Services may have links to third-party websites or applications, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own.  We are not responsible for the practices of such sites or applications.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

Protecting children’s privacy is important to us.  We do not direct the Services to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**

We have taken certain physical, administrative, and technical steps to safeguard the information we collect from and about Services visitors and users.  While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.

**IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or the practices described herein, you may contact us at [contact@brostrick.com](mailto:contact@brostrick.com%22%20%5Ct%20%22_blank).

**REVISIONS TO THIS STATEMENT**

Brostrick reserves the right to revise this Privacy Statement at any time.  When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Services.  If we change the Privacy Statement in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.
